[Music]
we live in an uncertain and
unpredictable World it has become
extremely critical to plan today to
secure our tomorrow presenting ICICI
group guaranteed income for tomorrow
gift a savings plus insurance plan that
allows you to save systematically and
grow your money with 100 guaranteed
tax-free returns while also giving you a
life cover to ensure your loved ones are
financially secure even in your absence
whether you are a millennial looking to
start your investment Journey
a regular investor looking for fixed
tax-free returns
A working woman looking to create a
second income stream a parent saving for
your child's education a businessman
securing your retirement
or an achiever who wants to fulfill his
goal of buying a house car or even going
on that dream vacation a savings plan
like gift forms an integral part of your
financial portfolio
the plan comes with three options income
early income and lump sum in this video
we will look at the gift income option
here you can set aside a fixed amount
from your income and invest for a
specific time period depending on your
goals and get a guaranteed flow of
income starting from the second year
after your contributions
let's understand this better with an
example
akhi Sharma is a 35 year old I.T
professional who is married and has two
children anticipating his family
which he is looking to create a second
resource of income Rakesh decides to
purchase the ICICI 2 gift plan he makes
an investment of rupees 1 lakh every
year for 10 years in the gift income
option online and selects annual payout
mode
he will get a guaranteed income of
rupees 2.05 lakh per year from the 12th
year onwards for the next 10 years this
means that with a payment of rupees 10
lakh he will get a guaranteed overall
sum of rupees 20.52 lakh in return
almost double of his investment
and the best part this return is fixed
and risk-free irrespective of
unpredictable Market scenarios
Mr Sharma will also get the dual benefit
of tax savings on premiums paid and
tax-free Returns on maturity moreover he
can get income when he wants with a
unique save the date feature he can also
Avail a loan against his policy in case
of any financial needs and lastly along
with regular income this plan also gives
Mr Sharma a life cover to secure the
well-being of his family in case of any
unfortunate event buying the gift plan
online is safe secure and convenient
plus you get to enjoy additional 2.5
percent maturity benefit visit
icicipruelife.com to know more benefits
about the plan today or call us at
1-800-209-977 and our insurance experts
will be glad to assist you
foreign
[Music]